Lawrence Ogbeifun

Department of Economics

Résumé

I am a PhD candidate in Economics at the University of Mississippi. My research interests lie in macroeconomics and span time series analysis, labor, monetary, and environmental economics. I am particularly interested in labor market reform in a dynamic and stochastic general equilibrium (DSGE) framework. I strive to answer questions in my research that are both academically interesting and policy relevant.

Education

2017–2023 U r	niversity of Mississippi,	Ph.D.,	Economics,	Expected	March 2023.
----------------------	---------------------------	--------	------------	----------	-------------

- 2017–2019 University of Mississippi, M.A., Economics.
- Summer 2020 **University of California (Virtual)**, *Berkeley/Sloan Summer School*, Environmental and Energy Economics.
 - 2021 **Tekedia Institute (Virtual)**, *Mini-MBA*.
- Summer 2021 **Dynare (Virtual)**, Dynare Summer School.
 - 2015–2016 University of Lagos, Nigeria, M.Sc., Economics.
 - 2009–2012 University of Benin, Nigeria, B.Sc., Mathematics and Economics.

Experience

2021-present **Instructor**, *University of Mississippi*.

Managed course material, assignments, and exams

2019–2022 **Teaching Assistant**, *University of Mississippi*.

- Undergraduate Level Experimental Economics
- Graduate Level Macroeconomics
- Graduate Level Econometrics

2017–2020 **Research Assistant**, *University of Mississippi*.

- Collecting and analyzing data
- Develop original quantitative research projects

Summer 2020 **Teaching Fellow**, *Michigan State University*, America Economic Association Summer Program.

Organized recitation lectures and assignments for classes

Honors and Awards

- Summer Research Assistantship, Graduate School, University of Mississippi, 2022.
- The National Opinion Research Center, 2022.
- o Graduate Student Award, Southern Economic Association, Fall 2021.
- o Graduate Assistantship, 2017–2023.

1/2 Lawrence Ogbeifun

Service

2017–2018 Graduate Student Council Senator, University of Mississippi.

• Representing economics graduate students

2017–2018 Volunteer, University of Mississippi.

o Green Grove Gameday Recycling Program

Computer Skills

MATLAB Advanced Stata Advanced
R Advanced LATEX Advanced
MS-Office Advanced E-views Advanced
Python Intermediate MySQL Intermediate

Tableau Basic RATs Basic

2/2 Lawrence Ogbeifun